Michael, could you help me, please?
迈克  请问你可以帮我一下吗
Sure. What is it?
当然可以  怎么了
We are going to have a soccer game against Class Five on Saturday.
我们周六将和五班有一场足球比赛
But one of my teammates fell ill. Will you join us?
但我们有一个队员生病了  你能加入我们吗
I'd be glad to. But I am not very good at it. Would you mind teaching me?
我很愿意加入  但我不太擅长  你能教教我吗
Not at all. You can do it!
没问题  你可以的
Let's go and practice.
我们去练习一下吧
Kangkang and Michael are practicing on the playground.
康康和迈克在操场上练习足球
Michael, I kick the ball to you. And you pass me the ball like this.
迈克  我把球踢给你  你这样传球给我
Sorry, I missed it.
抱歉  我错过了球
Never mind. Keep trying. I'll kick you the ball again.
没事  继续尝试  我会再把球踢给你
OK.
好的